Brother!
哥！
He had talent, but he was just human after all.
雖然他有資質，但畢竟是個人類
He breaks easily.
很容易就會壞掉
Move! Dammit!
滾開，可惡！
-Return him to the pit. -Move!
-要趁他還有氣 -別擋路！
-While he's alive. -Brother!
-把他送回洞裡 -哥！
-That is what we must do.
-我必須要這麼做
Because I have intelligence.
因為我可是有智慧的
Brother!
哥！
You shouldn't let your guard down, monster.
你大意了，怪物
Toma!
桐馬！
What are you doing over here?
你在那邊幹嘛？
Didn't I tell you to take care of the small fry?
我不是交代你解決那些小嘍囉了？
Yes… I'm sorry, Brother.
是…對不起，哥
His throat is regenerating. Why is that?
他的喉嚨再生了，怎麼會？
He should be an ordinary human… No.
他應該只是普通人類…不對
Could they have mixed with him in the pit?
難道他在洞裡的時候融合了？
Monster. I got a weird feeling from you earlier.
怪物，我一直 從你身上感受到奇怪的氣息
What was that?
那是什麼？
Is he talking about Tao? An ordinary human shouldn't be able to sense it…
他是在說道嗎？ 普通人類應該感覺不到
Come on! Are you out of dumb things to say?
怎麼？不敢多說嗎？
Or is whatever that was the true form of the monsters' powers?
難道說，那個東西 就是怪物的力量來源？
Is it the key to destroying Lord Tensen?
那就是打敗天仙的關鍵？
His Tao is much bigger than it was before…
這個男人的道比剛剛更強大了
I can feel it. This man is dangerous.
我感覺到了，這個男人很危險
I must kill him now.
必須馬上除掉他
I can't see it.
看不到
So much strength for this body…
這種體格居然有這樣的力道
That thing I felt must be the secret!
果然秘密就在那股氣息裡！
His Tao is increasing even more… Is it because of the vines?
他的道又變更多了 是受到藤蔓影響嗎？
He's gone beyond the limits of humanity.
他已經超越人類的極限
My brother is a genius at adapting.
我哥是適應狀況的天才
But at this rate… I don't think… he can handle much more…
但總覺得繼續這樣… 不能再繼續下去了…
I don't really know how…
雖然我不清楚狀況
But my body has become amazingly useful.
但我的身體似乎變得很好用呢
What courage you have. Are you not afraid of your body changing…
你真有勇氣，難道你都不害怕身體
that you may not be human anymore?
變得再也不像人類嗎？
Nope. Nothing in this world is unchanging.
不會啊，這世上本就沒有不變的東西
I know that better than anyone.
這點我比誰都更清楚
One thing that never changes is more than enough.
不變的東西有一個就足夠了
One thing? You mean yourself?
一個？說你自己嗎？
No…
不是…
-What are you doing? -Brother!
-你們要幹嘛？ -哥！
Your upbringing shows on your faces.
你們一臉富家子弟的樣子
You look too classy. People are underestimating us as your crew.
長得太斯文 當你們的同伴都會被人看不起
I'll have to make you fit the part.
我來讓你變得豪邁點
Starting with the younger brother.
就從弟弟開始吧
Huh?
什麼？
Are you crazy?! What are you doing?
你瘋了嗎？你幹什麼？
Do I look classy now?
這樣還斯文嗎？
If you still have complaints, make me look better.
誰還有意見的話，就過來對我動手啊
A monster wouldn't understand.
你這種怪物是不會懂的
No one understands.
沒有人會懂
Now, show me more of that power!
來啊，再讓我見識一下你那種妖術！
You… I knew it!
你…果然沒錯！
The navel is your weakness!
你的弱點果然是肚臍！
It's getting bigger and bigger… What is this man?
道越來越大了 這個男人究竟是什麼人？
I saw it…
我看得到了
I thought you were throwing weird stuff at me…
我一直覺得你往我這邊丟奇怪的東西
But it's all over your body too.
但你身體周遭全都是那個東西
-Soshin! To me-- -Oh…
-竈神，往我這邊… -抱歉了
That's not possible.
那是不可能的
Since I killed them all.
因為我已經殺光光了
Come on! Show me more of that power!
來啊，再多露幾手給我看看！
Reveal your hand!
讓我看清楚你的把戲！
I see… So that's how you gather it.
原來如此，這樣做就能凝聚了吧
But even though it's all around you, it doesn't increase your defense?
雖然你渾身都被包住 但是那東西沒有防禦效果嗎？
-I took you down easily. -This ridiculous…
-這麼容易就被我踩爛了 -怎麼可能…
When I fought that other guy, my attacks were pretty much useless.
跟天仙對戰的時候 我的攻擊幾乎都沒有效果
Is it because I didn't have any around me?
是因為我身上沒有包那個嗎？
Impossible…
不可能…
I feel like there's a lot more to it.
感覺應該還要往下研究
Well, I guess I just have to try.
看來只能實際試試看了
Is this Tao?
這個就是道？
Impossible!
不可能啊！
Look at that! Seems like you can be killed.
什麼嘛？果然你是殺得死的
I can see all the Tao of your dying body!
我已經能全看到了 你垂死身體周遭的道！
Get up, monster!
給我起來，怪物！
I have so many questions I want to ask you.
我還有很多問題想問你
First, where is Lord Tensen?
先告訴我天仙在哪裡
Somehow it looks like he's got more scars…
是錯覺嗎？傷疤看起來好像變多了
What's up?
怎麼了？
Hey, what are you spacing out for?
喂，你發什麼呆啊？
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Help me tie him up.
幫我把他綁起來
Am I seeing things?
是我看錯了？
For now I'm glad that he's still alive, but…
雖然很慶幸哥哥還活著，可是…
Is he really okay?
他真的不要緊嗎？
And those scars… They look like lacerations.
而且這些傷疤不像裂痕
Or like a plant…
很像是植物
Like the vines of a plant…
就像植物的藤蔓一樣…
What do you think, Little Lady? Is my swordsmanship cool or what?
怎麼樣，小姐？我的劍術很強吧？
Strong…
強…
That Tao thing will come easily for me, don't you think?
妳不覺得我可以 馬上學會那個什麼道嗎？
Tao… Strong, weak.
道…強，弱
Strong, strong bad.
強，強，不行
I don't get it.
我不懂妳的意思
-How about this? -Strong, strong bad!
-是這樣嗎？ -強，強，不行！
-Or this? -Strong, strong!
-還是這樣？ -強，強！
Tao… Strong, weak.
道…強，弱
This conversation is impossible.
這對話怎麼好像機智問答？
Are you telling me brute force is bad?
光靠蠻力是不行的嗎？
He's pretty good for being so small.
他雖然矮小，但真的很能打
What about him, Little Lady?
小姐，那他呢？
Strong, strong. Bad, bad.
強，強，不行…
The Hollow and The Blade Dragon…
空空如也的伽藍跟劍龍
They're both so reliable!
他們還真可靠！
What are you doing?
你這是在幹嘛？
I'm analyzing the monsters.
分析怪物
Each one is different, with a different internal structure.
每個怪物的身體構造都不同
Even though they're similar,
儘管外型相似
this one's internal structure is like a fish's
這個的內部構造像魚
and this one's like a human.
而這個的就像人類
So?
所以呢？
Everyone's weak point is different.
每一隻的要害都不一樣
It's pretty mysterious from a biological standpoint…
從生物學來說很難解釋…
And she's the same way. What even is she?
還有她也是 那個女孩究竟是什麼人？
She used some kind of power to shave down the cliff and escape.
那時她用了某種力量 在山崖上挖出往下逃跑的路
That's what it looked like.
至少我看起來是這樣
A normal human wouldn't be able to do that.
普通人類根本做不到
A normal human…
普通人類…
I made her cry again… So she's still a child inside.
我又讓她哭了，看來內在依舊是小孩
Hey, ninja!
喂，忍者！
Don't make the Little Lady cry!
不准惹小姐哭！
You won't win the ladies with a look like that!
眼神那麼兇惡會沒女人緣喔！
I don't want any ladies. I'm a married man.
沒女人緣也無所謂，我已經有家室了
What?
-什麼？
That's not what I mean!
我不是那個意思！
If you want to be my sidekick, you can't make ladies cry!
要當我的小弟就不可以惹女孩子哭！
I'm not your sidekick.
我又不是你小弟
He's more human than the rumors say, this "Hollow"…
伽藍堂比傳聞中還有人情味呢
Strong, strong, strong! Bad!
強，強，強，不行！
Do you have a wife?
倒是你，你娶妻了嗎？
I have…
那是…
a woman in every corner of the country!
我在全國各地都有女人
I have been secretly looking for you, Lady Mei.
我們一直在 暗中尋找您的下落，芽衣大人
"Lady" Mei…?
芽衣…“大人”？
It has been several hundred years since you were expelled from the castle.
數百年前，您被驅逐出城
You have not been seen in Horai.
從此在蓬萊銷聲匿跡
We were at a loss as to where to find you.
我們根本不知道該從何找起
Lord Rien ordered us not to look for you…
蓮大人下令要我們不要尋找您
It is good fortune that I meet you here.
能夠在這裡見到您真是無比幸運
I am filled with emotion.
小人心中充滿感動
Now, let us return together.
請跟小人一道回去吧
We need your assistance.
我們需要您的協助
What is going on?
這是怎麼回事？
That is what I would like to know. I do not know how it got this way,
那正是我要問的 我不清楚事情如何發展至此
but she is not a being that should be consorting with humans like you.
但這位大人 不是你們這種人類可以隨意靠近的
She is the same rank as Lord Tensen.
梅大人的地位等同天仙大人
Humans are merely nutrition for the likes of her.
人類對她而言就只是養分
Tensen? The one we talked about?
天仙？是之前講的那個？
Is she the same?
她是同類嗎？
So she isn't human…
她果然不是人類
Please return to Horai and show us the way.
請回到蓬萊領導我們吧
Without your help, we are…
沒有您的協助，我們就…
If I keep getting bogged down with all this trouble
繼續跟這些麻煩事糾纏不清的話
I'll lose sight of the goal.
就會看不清前方目標了
I need to figure out what she wants, why she helped me…
必須搞清楚我本來的目的 她所扮演的角色
And what I need to do now.
還有我現在應該怎麼做
What are you doing, human?
你這是做什麼，人類？
Well… I don't know.
不是，我不自覺就…
If your intention is to help her, it is misplaced.
如果你以為 這樣是為她好，那你就錯了
This is our problem.
這是我們自己的事
Well, yeah, that's true.
說得也是
I don't know what's going on, so this might be rash.
我不清楚內情，這樣做或許太莽撞
This isn't really my style anyway, and it's kind of a pain.
這也不是我的作風，說真的，好麻煩
I didn't expect myself to be so impulsive.
我也沒想到我會這麼衝動
But…
不過…
I don't want her to cry again.
我不想再讓她哭了
Let's leave it at that.
對我而言，這點理由就足夠了
What a terrible inconvenience.
真是礙事
In any case, we came here to turn you into Tan.
不管怎樣 我們本來就要把你們做成丹
Where did…?
他什麼時候…
We will bring Lady Mei home.
芽衣大人會跟我們回去
Is that one the leader of the butterflies?
那傢伙就是蝴蝶的首領嗎？
I'll kill him.
我絕對要幹掉他
Based on their appearance, these guys must be bug handlers.
從外型來看 這些傢伙可能會操縱蟲子
Or… possibly their leaders?
不然他們就是蟲子的頭目
I better not get too close.
最好別靠太近
I lost my left hand because of these guys.
害我失去左手的就是蝴蝶
I better show them my thanks.
我可要好好感激他們一番
Where is my thanks?
那你也要好好謝謝我囉？
I was the one who reconstruc-- healed your hand.
是我改造了…是我治療你的手的
I'm pretty sure it's a figure of speech.
我想他說的不是你想的那個意思
No, I'm serious.
沒有，我是認真的
Losing my hand has sharpened my abilities even further.
世間萬物皆能被失去磨鍊得更進步
My sword is even stronger than before!
我的劍術比之前更強了！
-What? -The invisible attack I saw before?
-什麼？ -是之前那種看不到的攻擊？
They can use it too…
他們也會用
Don't just charge in. They have some sort of invisible power.
不要莽撞亂衝 那些傢伙會某種奇怪的術
I see. That must be Tao.
原來如此，那就是道
These bugs are incessant!
沒完沒了的臭蟲子！
Stay out of my way, sidekick!
當小弟的別礙事！
I'm not your sidekick, and you're the one in the way.
我不是你小弟，而且礙事的人是你
I'm trying to kill that butterfly!
我要殺了那個蝴蝶人！
You are not our opponents.
你們不是我們的對手
You should have no connection to Lady Mei.
芽衣大人跟你們毫無關係
Why do you try to protect her?
為什麼要護著她？
True…
沒錯
The old me might have left her by the wayside.
以前的我大概就丟下她不管了
Since stepping foot on this island, I've done many things that were unlike me.
自從踏上這座島之後 我老是做出不像自己的事
But… I don't think it's bad.
但…感覺並不糟糕
When you owe someone a favor, you help them.
別人對我有恩，當然該出手幫忙
That's obvious.
這是理所當然的
I'd ask the same of you. Why are you so fixated on her?
倒是你們 為什麼這麼堅持要抓走她？
It looks like she doesn't like you.
她看起來不願意跟你們走
We are beings who study and practice Tao.
我們道士的目的 就是道的學習與修練
Lady Mei is an important, indispensable figure in our training.
在我們的修行裡 芽衣大人是不可或缺的存在
A monster like you actually training?
你們這種怪物也會修行？
Tao is inherent in all things.
道蘊含於萬物之中
Foolish, pitiful humans,
你們這群愚昧可悲的人類
I will teach you before you become Tan.
在你們變成丹之前，我就告訴你們吧
There are five trainings that increase your Tao.
提升道的修練方式有五種
Doin, Taisoku, Shuitsu, Shuten,
導引、胎息、守一、周天
and the most important, Bochu Jutsu.
還有最重要的房中術
Bochu Jutsu requires a partner,
房中術需要有對象才能練習
as it circulates Yin and Yang through a physical union.
因為需要透過身體結合來讓陰陽循環
What does "physical union" mean?
“身體結合”是什麼意思？
Put simply, it's sexual intercourse.
簡單來說，就是性交
What?!
什麼？
So doing it is a type of training? Ridiculous.
做愛是修行？真荒唐
It is a sublime training.
那是種崇高的修行
All things in nature possess the energy of either Yin or Yang.
自然萬物必屬於陰陽兩極之一
When these polar opposites are looped in a cycle, Tao increases.
兩極循環之時，道就會變多
Doin, Taisoku, and the other practices prepare the mind and body,
以導引、胎息等技巧調整身心
and then Yin and Yang join and become a cycle.
接著讓陰陽雙方結合開始循環
That is Bochu Jutsu.
那就是房中術
The heightened Tao that results
這種方式修行的道可以賦予
gives one the ability to change the natural way of the world.
一個人足以顛覆天地的力量
The one who has achieved the pinnacle of this practice
目前在這方面的修行 已至巔峰造極之境者
is our master, Lord Tensen.
就是我們的師尊，天仙大人
Lord Tensen is transcendent existence. They have not only
天仙大人已經是超脫一切的存在
mastered Bochu Jutsu, but have both Yin and Yang circulating within themselves.
除了房中術 還能不靠他人就可以進行陰陽循環
With the repeated circulation of Yin and Yang,
將陰陽反覆循環
they can transform and raise their Tao.
不斷轉換型態進而提升道行
In order to reach the highest level of Tao,
為了追求巔峰的道
they have devoted themselves to training for a thousand years.
千年來，天仙大人們致力於修行
Their Yin and Yang manifests as gender.
陰陽會以性別呈現出來
Lord Tensen possesses both extremes in one person.
天仙大人可以一人同時擁有兩者
The circulation of polar opposite Yin and Yang…
陰陽兩極的循環…
Changing between a man and a woman…
在男女之間變換…
However, ordinary beings possess only one.
但是一般生物只能擁有其中一種
Therefore, in order to circulate both Yin and Yang, they need a partner.
因此，若要進行 陰陽循環，就需要對象
We are male-- Yang energy.
我們是雄性，也就是陽
Lady Mei is Yin, and she possesses special Yin energy.
芽衣大人是陰 而且她擁有特別的陰氣
The joining and circulation of our Yang and her Yin
讓我們的陽氣 與芽衣大人的陰氣循環
is Bochu Jutsu training.
就是房中術修行
Are you saying…?
你們是說…
Don't say it out loud. It's revolting.
別說了，太噁心了
Lady Mei descends from the same lineage as Lord Tensen,
芽衣大人與天仙大人雖系出同源
but is inferior as she possesses only Yin.
但她卻只擁有陰，是次級品
Therefore, she was banished from the castle.
因此才被驅逐出城
Lord Rien granted Lady Mei two options.
蓮大人給了芽衣大人兩個選擇
Die like a dog by the roadside,
像野狗一樣死在路邊
or remain in Horai as our training partner.
或是留在蓬萊當我們道士的修練對象
Lady Mei's scars are from the hand of Lord Rien.
芽衣大人的傷疤是蓮大人留下的
They brand her for her role.
是把她當成修行對象的記號
However, Lady Mei disappeared from Horai.
然而，芽衣大人卻從蓬萊消失了
Please return, for the sake of our training.
為了我們的修行，拜託您回來吧
Now I understand why the Little Lady was so afraid.
我現在明白小姐為何會害怕了
You guys are creepy and gross.
你們真是噁心得要命
As if a human could understand.
人類不可能理解仙道
Hey ninja, I've got the centipede if--
忍者，那隻蜈蚣也交給我…
I haven't been myself since I arrived.
登島之後，我就一直不像我
No…
不對
I was just about to see a version of myself I never knew.
應該說是一直發現我不認識的自己
I'm a little surprised.
有點訝異呢
It looks like I can't allow that.
看來我也無法容忍這種事
A brand…
你說“記號”？
Stop talking about her like she's an object.
別把她說得像是物品一樣
So that's how it will be.
這樣啊
It seems turning you into Tan will be difficult.
看來很難把你們做成丹了
Senjutsu: False-Kishikai.
仙術，擬鬼屍解
You will all die here!
既然如此，就在這裡殺掉你們！
You can try!
放馬過來啊！
Seems like Sennin can transform into yokai monsters.
看來仙人可以變身成妖怪
Lord Tensen also transformed into a monster…
天仙大人也會變成怪物
Is this the same art?
是相同的妖術嗎？
I can't lose this fight.
這一仗不能輸
Your lumpy parts are easier to dodge!
你們聚成一塊，我更容易躲開
I'm dizzy…
好暈…
Did I breathe in some bug dust?
難道是吸到蟲子的鱗粉了？
Fighting them is a serious challenge.
那傢伙還真是難對付
-Sidekick! I need your assistance! -I can't!
-小弟，掩護我！ -辦不到！
It's hard… but…
很硬…不過
It can burn.
可以燒
Senjutsu: Tin Splinter!
仙術，鈴刺！
Its attacks aren't as powerful as Lord Tensen's,
威力雖不如天仙大人的攻擊
but I can't see them.
但我一樣看不到
Those butterflies are dangerous, Chibimaru.
那些蝴蝶很危險，矮子丸
Ninja Art: Fire Bridge!
忍法，火橋
Stop.
住手
We could harm Lady Mei with such poor visibility.
看不清楚的話，可能會傷到芽衣大人
Invisible power… Tao…
看不見的力量…道…
I can feel it faintly.
我能隱約感覺到道
If I can't get a good sense of it, I can't win.
但如果不能清楚察覺到道，就打不贏
And I can't afford to lose against this opponent.
我可不能輸給這種程度的對手
The real fight is yet to come.
真正的對手是天仙那傢伙
If I could just understand what she said…
要是能理解那女孩說的話就好了
You're focusing too much on strength, I think.
我想你太過聚焦於力量了
To see Tao,
要看見道
strength and weakness must coexist in your mind.
強與弱必須並存於心中
How do you know?
你是怎麼知道的？
Just as Sugita Genpaku and his colleagues
就像杉田玄白跟他的同儕
translated Ontleedkundige Tafelen on their own,
以自學的方式翻譯《解體新書》一樣
I deciphered what she was saying and had her demonstrate.
我試著解讀她說的話，並且請她示範
I had her access my Tao directly.
我讓她直接觸碰我的道
It helped me sense it for myself.
幫助我直接感受自身的道
I can feel something,
確實可以感覺到什麼
but that's it. I don't see anything.
但就只有這樣，我還是看不到
In order to see Tao, you have to train,
要看見道，就必須要修行
and put your mind in a very specific state.
讓心靈維持在一種特定狀態
You, Gabimaru,
特別是畫眉丸你
have to weaken your mind.
必須讓心靈變弱
Weaken it? But we're in the middle of a battle.
變弱？可是現在在戰鬥中耶
Even so.
就算這樣也要
Tao is like a visualization of life force.
道是讓生命力能被看見的力量
Without both strength and weakness, you won't sense it.
強弱兼具才能夠感覺到它
Weaken my mind?
讓心靈變弱？
Strength is the fruit of weakness.
強是弱的成果
Weakness is the seed of strength.
弱是強的種子
That is not weakness. That is the seed of strength.
這不是軟弱，這是強大的種子
Strength, weakness… It's all… important.
強與弱…都很重要
Well, it's not something you can master in a day.
不過，這不是一朝一夕就能學會的
No.
不
That's enough. I've got the gist.
夠了，我大概懂了
What? What do you mean? Hey--
什麼？“大概懂了”？等等…
Hey, wait!
你…你等等！
-Big. -Huh?
-很大 -什麼？
Gabimaru's… Tao is… big.
畫眉丸…道，很大
That sensation.
那種感覺…
Senjutsu: Tin Splinter!
仙術，鈴刺！
He's dodging… He understood it just from that?
他都躲過了，只聽那種說明就懂了？
He's an Iwagakure Ninja.
那傢伙可是石隱村的忍者
I've heard some members have otherworldly powers.
聽說他們有人擁有超乎常人的力量
He may not have heard the word Tao before…
或許他之前沒有聽過道這個詞
but I wouldn't be surprised if he knew something similar.
但他可能已經學會類似的東西
This is the true nature of Gabimaru the Hollow.
這才是伽藍的畫眉丸的真本事
The result of training that makes you discard your humanity.
這是他捨棄人性，潛心修行的成果吧
Based on the Tao's movement, I can read each attack's intent and course.
我可以從道的動向 判斷攻擊的意圖與路線
I can also clearly sense what's behind me.
也能清楚感受我身後的氣息
This is the same sensation as when I couldn't attain
這並不是我在石隱村的修行
any of the techniques drilled into me at Iwagakure.
可以得到的成果 我不曾有過這種感受
It's not just the strong auras…
不只是強大的氣息
I can feel the weak auras too. I can feel everything around me!
還有弱小的氣息也是 一切都能感受得到！
By accepting my own weakness…
因為接納了我自己的弱
I could sense the weaknesses of those around me…
所以才能感受到周圍的弱
Right?
是這樣嗎？
In between my stubborn heart and my delicate heart…
處在頑強的心與纖弱的心之間
Or their coexistence.
或是兩者並存
It's like I'm in wave of conflict.
感覺好像處在搖擺的海浪上
I understand now.
我現在懂了
Her strength can go on without hesitation.
那個女人就算迷惘也能前進的強大
Even stronger… Even weaker…
越來越強…越來越弱…
The Tao of each and every bug on his arm…
他手臂上每隻小蟲子的道
I can tell the intent and course.
我都能讀出意志跟方向
Like I know how a single drop of water
好比我知道落入水中的小石子
can hit its surroundings and create a huge ripple.
如何與周遭碰撞並製造出漣漪
Ninja arts?
是忍術嗎？
No… This feat is impossible for humans. It's like…
不對，人類怎麼可能做到？簡直像…
Like… A Tensen!
像天仙…
You can't beat me now.
你們贏不了了
Now I'm finally in the same ring as Lord Tensen.
這下總算有資格跟天仙大人打了吧
That he was able to perceive Tao in such a short time…
竟然在這麼短的時間內 就學會察覺道的方法
The accuracy of his attack…
攻擊如此精準
Speak.
快招
Where are the others? Where is Lord Tensen?
其他同夥呢？天仙大人在哪裡？
It is the end for me. I shall answer.
看來到此為止了，我就告訴你吧
Including me, there are three Doshi
包括我在內，共有三名道士
who were ordered to scout out the humans by Lord Tensen.
奉天仙大人之命出來偵察人類
They believed that there was something different about the newest arrivals.
因為大人認為 這次登島的人類與以往不同
If left alone,
要是放任不管的話
their fangs could've come for our throats.
這種威脅最終會近在眼前
It seems that was correct.
看來大人的擔憂果然沒錯
Wait!
等等！
The sidekick cannot outshine the star!
哪有小弟搶走主角光環的？
I will deal the finishing blow!
就由我來了結他！
I'm not a sidekick!
我不是你小弟！
Ninja Art: Thunder Stones
忍法，雷礫…
Centipede Version!
蜈蚣附魔！
Is this…
這裡是…
Horai?
蓬萊？
WELCOME
（歡迎光臨）
Subtitle translation by: Mel Nishi
字幕翻譯：洪貞韻